Preliminary Guide to the Washington State University College of Engineering Research Division Correspondence, Minutes, Reports, and Speeches circa 1940s-1970
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- The use of Arabogalactan in the Lithograhic Industry (Box 7, Folder 325)
- Arabogalactan in Textile Sizing (Box 7, Folder 326)
- Report on Trip to Sinclair and Valentine Co., Dayton, Ohio (Box 7, Folder 327)
- Report on Market Development Trip on Arabogalactan (Box 7, Folder 328)
- Purification of Technical Arabogalactan (Box 7, Folder 329)
- Fact Sheet on Arabogalactan (Box 7, Folder 330)
- Preliminary Design and Cost Estimate 1000 Pound Per Day Arabogalactan Pilot Plant (Box 7, Folder 331)
- Particle Size Separation and Identification of Clay (Box 7, Folder 332)
- Particle Size Separation and Identification of Clay (Box 7, Folder 333)
- X-Ray Difraction Measurements on Magnesite (Box 7, Folder 334)
- Chemical and Heat Resistant Coating for Metal and Masonry (Box 7, Folder 335)
- Chemical and Heat Resistant Coating for Metal and Masonry (Box 7, Folder 336)
- Water Analysis (Box 7, Folder 337)
- Water Irrigation (Box 7, Folder 338)
- Spectrographic Copper Analysis (Box 7, Folder 339)
- Evaluation of Blind Fastness for Prefinished Siding (Box 7, Folder 340)
- Oxide Determination in Ferro Chrome (Box 7, Folder 341)
- Performance Tests and Evaluation of Packard Water Conditioner (Box 7, Folder 342)
- Performance Tests and Evaluation of Packard Water Conditioner (Box 7, Folder 343)
- Gluing Problem in the R.A. Pearson Plant (Box 7, Folder 344)
- Glue Feeder for Tray Making Machine (Box 7, Folder 345)
- Examination of Oxide Zinc Ores (Pend Oreille Mines and Metals Co.) (Box 7, Folder 346)
- Combustion of Lye Peeled Potato Residue (Box 7, Folder 347)
- Special Investigation of Weld Metal: Case No. 34252 (Box 7, Folder 348)
- Arson Investigation (Box 7, Folder 349)
- Efficiency Study of Mixers of Particle Board (Box 7, Folder 350)
- The Influence of Forest Site on the Wood Properties of Western Conifers (Potlach Forests, Inc.) (Box 7, Folder 351)
- A Study of the Mechanical Properties of Construction Lumber (Potlach Forests, Inc.) (Box 7, Folder 352)
- Round Butte Spillway Model Portland General Electric (Box 7, Folder 353)
- Round Butte Trifurcation Model (Box 7, Folder 354)
- Comparison of the Mechanical Properties of Inland and Coast- Type Douglas Fir and Western Larch Plywood (Box 7, Folder 355)
- Leaching and Chemical Tests on Fiber Containers for Pure Food and Drug Acceptance Purposes (Box 7, Folder 356)
- Dimensional Stability and Glue Line Behavior of Plyfloor (Potlach Forests, Inc.) (Box 7, Folder 357)
- Load Transfer Characteristics of Tongue-and-Groove Joints (Box 7, Folder 358)
- Haunch Joint Testing (Box 7, Folder 359)
- Testing Joist Lumber (Box 7, Folder 360)
- Ore Analysis (Box 7, Folder 361)
- Police Investigation (Box 7, Folder 362)
- Brick Mortar Problem (Box 7, Folder 363)
- The Effect of Furafilasan Additive for Plywood Adhesives (Box 7, Folder 364)
- Corrosion Survey (Box 7, Folder 365)
- Investigation of Leather Reconditioner (Box 7, Folder 366)
- Analysis of Fuel Oil and Boiler Ash (Box 7, Folder 367)
- Investigation of the Torque Characteristics of Aerospace Ball Bearings at Minus 65 F After Oxidation of Lubricant (Box 7, Folder 368)
- Electron Microscopy Study of Missile Greases (Box 7, Folder 369)
- Simulated Exposure Studies of Factory-Applied Primer on Cedar Siding (Box 7, Folder 370)
- Basic Research on Very Fine Particle Fraction of Bovill Clays (Box 7, Folder 371)
- Basic and Applied Research towards improving brightness of Bovill Clay (Box 7, Folder 372)
- Moisture Permeability of 1/4" Plywood containing aluminum foil (Simpson Timber Co.) (Box 7, Folder 373)
- Particle Board Survey - European Development and Practice (Box 7, Folder 374)
- Physical Properties of Brownsville Exterior Particleboard (Box 7, Folder 375)
- Evaluation of Simpson Sheathing with Staple-Type Fastening (Box 7, Folder 376)
- Arson Investigation (Box 7, Folder 377)
- Wear Rate Processes for Five Gear Lubricants (Southwestern Petroleum Company) 11/1/1960 (Box 7, Folder 378)
- Transmission Conductor Creep Measurements (Box 7, Folder 379)
- Transmission Conductor Creep Measurements (Box 7, Folder 380)
- Arson Investigation (Capt. James Bell - Spokane Fire Dept.) (Box 7, Folder 381)
- Spokane Monroe Street Explosion (Box 7, Folder 382)
- Monroe Street Explosion Investigation (Box 7, Folder 383)
- Police Investigation Case No. 246084 - Spokane Safe and Lock (Box 7, Folder 384)
- Police Investigation - Spokane Murder Case (Box 7, Folder 385)
- Three-Frequency Backscatter Radar and Riometer Observations During IGC-1959 (Box 7, Folder 386)
- Water Analysis (Box 7, Folder 387)
- Wallace Swimming Pool (Box 7, Folder 388)
- Wallace Swimming Pool (Box 7, Folder 389)
- Pivot Lubricant "A:" for Tally Register Corporation (Box 7, Folder 390)
- Preparation of Tally Type A Grease (Box 7, Folder 391)
- Oil Sample Analysis (Box 7, Folder 392)
- Flexibility, Friction and Wear Characteristics of Diffusion Lubricated Teleflex Alloys (Box 7, Folder 393)
- Flexibility, Friction and Wear Characteristics of Diffusion Lubricated Teleflex Alloys (Box 7, Folder 394)
- Teleflex Lubricants Investigation (Box 7, Folder 395)
- Development of Lubricants for Servo Mechanism Control Cables for Use at 1000 F to 1500 F (Box 7, Folder 396)
- Development of Lubricants for Servo Mechanism Control Cables for Use at 1000 F to 1500 F (Box 7, Folder 397)
- Analyze small sample of grain for poison (Sheriff, Clarence A. Van Allen) (Box 7, Folder 398)
- Feasibility Study of New Wood Floor Constructions Designs (Box 7, Folder 399)
- Acoustic Noise Reduction (Extension It 1) (Turbo Ind.) (Box 7, Folder 400)
- Acoustic Noise Reduction - Turbo Industries, Inc. (Box 7, Folder 401)
- Study of Binders for TC Board (Box 7, Folder 402)
- Development of Law Friction Alloy Valve Sleeve for 200-930 F Applications (Box 7, Folder 403)
- Development of Low Friction Alloy Valve Sleeve for 200-930 F Applications (Box 7, Folder 404)
- Properties of Vapor-Deposited Films (United Control Corp.) (Box 7, Folder 405)
- Analysis of Water Deposits (Box 7, Folder 406)
- Thunderstorm Center Flood Studies (Box 7, Folder 407)
- Spectroanalysis of Ore Sample (Box 7, Folder 408)
- Arson Investigation (Box 7, Folder 409)
- Development of and Insecticidal Fog Oil Base Stock (Box 7, Folder 410)
- Examination of Crankcase Oil (Box 7, Folder 411)
- Analysis of Wheat Dust (Police Investigation) (Box 7, Folder 412)
- Police Investigation - Odessa Tank Explosion (Box 7, Folder 413)
- Spectrochemical Analysis of McCammon Ore Sample (Box 7, Folder 414)
- Corrosion Study on Domestic Pump (Box 7, Folder 415)
- Corrosion Study on Domestic Pump (Box 7, Folder 416)
- Squaw Rapids Cofferdam (Box 7, Folder 417)
- Oil Analysis (Box 7, Folder 418)
- Determination of Foreign Material in Oil (Box 7, Folder 419)
- Water Analysis (Box 7, Folder 420)
- Water Analysis (Box 7, Folder 421)
- Spokane Valley Groundwater Pollution Study (Box 7, Folder 422)
- Sacramento, California Network Analysis (Box 7, Folder 423)
- Police Investigation (Box 7, Folder 424)
- Wanapum Hydroelectric Project Final Closure Studies (Box 7, Folder 425)
- Cofferdam Studies - Wanapum Dam (Box 7, Folder 426)
- Moscow Ground Water Survey (Box 7, Folder 427)
- Moscow Ground Water Survey (Box 7, Folder 428)
- Arson Investigation (Moses Lake) (Box 7, Folder 429)
- Arson Investigation (Box 7, Folder 430)
- Solid-Phase Lubricants for the 1000 F to 1800 F Range (Box 8, Folder 431)
- Fluoride Analysis of Smith Brothers Leaf Samples II (Box 8, Folder 432)
- Fluoride Analysis of Smith Brothers Leaf Samples II (Box 8, Folder 433)
- Spokane Limed Filter Paper Data (Box 8, Folder 434)
- Indoor Limed Filter Paper Data (Box 8, Folder 435)
- Fluoride Analysis of Smith Brothers Leaf Samples (Box 8, Folder 436)
- Air Pollution in Cowlitz County (Box 8, Folder 437)
- An Automatic HF Recorder For Industrial Hygiene and Stack Monitoring (Box 8, Folder 438)
- A Quantitative Study of the Limed Filter Paper Technique for Fluorine Air Pollution Studies (Box 8, Folder 439)
- Unaccepted Proposals - Sponsored Work (Box 8, Folder 440)
- Unaccepted Proposals - Sponsored Work (Box 8, Folder 441)
- Unaccepted Proposals - Sponsored Work (Box 8, Folder 442)
- Unaccepted Proposals - Sponsored Work (Box 8, Folder 443)
- Unaccepted Proposals - Sponsored Work (Box 8, Folder 444)
- Unaccepted Proposals - Sponsored Work (Box 8, Folder 445)
- Unaccepted Proposals - Sponsored Work (Box 8, Folder 446)
- Unaccepted Proposals - Sponsored Work (Box 8, Folder 447)
- Unaccepted Proposals - Sponsored Work (Box 8, Folder 448)
- Unaccepted Proposals - Sponsored Work (Box 8, Folder 449)
- Proposal for An Investigation of the Fate of Radionucides in the Lower Columbia River (Box 8, Folder 450)
- Report by the Advisory Committee for the Hanford Columbia River Model (Box 8, Folder 451)
- An Analytical and Experimental Study of Fin Propellers (Box 8, Folder 452)
- Proposal for Design, Development and Research Contract DDR-65, Hydraulic Model Test (Box 8, Folder 453)
- Geological Investigation of Ground Water Potential in the Pullman Area Employing Seismic Methods (Box 8, Folder 454)
- An Outline for Proposed Research to Improve Magnetic Materials For High Temperature Operation (Box 8, Folder 455)
- Unaccepted proposals - Sponsored Work (Box 8, Folder 456)
- Correspondence 13J-3801-0996 (11E) (Box 8, Folder 457)
- Adams 2/73-12/73 13J-3801-0996 (Box 8, Folder 458)
- Contract IIN-3813-0960 Production of Min. Wool from Coal (Box 8, Folder 459)
- Adams 6/67-12/71 13J-3801-0996 (Box 8, Folder 460)
- Agreements 13J-3801-0996 (IIE) (Box 8, Folder 461)
- Hurd 8/58-6168 IIN-3802-0326 Research Reports (Box 8, Folder 462)
- 381 E 15 (Box 8, Folder 463)
- Cost Reports 1963/1964 (Box 8, Folder 464)
- Urgent Deadlines (Box 9, Folder 465)
- Section Head Meetings (Box 9, Folder 466)
- Adcom Meetings (Box 9, Folder 467)
- Advisory Board Meetings (Box 9, Folder 468)
- Idea Implementation (Box 9, Folder 469)
- To Do (Box 9, Folder 470)
- Administrative Staff Meeting (Box 9, Folder 471)
- Cost Cutting Programs (Box 9, Folder 472)
- Presentations to Legislature (Box 9, Folder 473)
- Supporting Data for Budget Cut Restoration to ERD (Box 9, Folder 474)
- Statistics on ERD Salaries Related to State/Sponsor Salary Support (Box 9, Folder 475)
- Division Budget Request 1971-73 Biennium Submitted 1/26/70 (Box 9, Folder 476)
- Resolutions Press Interviews Informal Statements (Box 9, Folder 477)
- Governor's Proposed Budget for ERD - Administrative WSU Budget Analysis (Box 9, Folder 478)
- Planned Staff and Operations Reductions ERD for 1971-73 Based on (a) Governor's Budget 1/71, (b) Legislation's Restoration 5/71 (Box 9, Folder 479)
- 1971/73 Section Requests (Box 9, Folder 480)
- On Initiation of Research Projects Engineering Research Division 381A 6.8 (Box 9, Folder 481)
- Administration - Personnel - Advisory Board - Policy (Box 9, Folder 482)
- 381A 6.8 WSU Research Policy (Box 9, Folder 483)
- Comments on Study Council Reports on Engineering Research Division (Box 9, Folder 484)
- Biennium 1973-75 - Call for Forecasts and Requests - Engineering Research Division (Box 9, Folder 485)
- Biennium 1973-75 Section Requests (Box 9, Folder 486)
- Oil Analysis (Box 10, Folder 487)
- ** Grinding Calcined Shale (Box 10, Folder 488)
- Flow Distribution - Olympia Water System (Box 10, Folder 489)
- Fundamental Studies on Air Oxidation of Molibdenum at Low Pressures and Elevated Temperatures (Box 10, Folder 490)
- Fundamental Studies on Air Oxidation of Molibdenum at Low Pressures and Elevated Temperatures (Box 10, Folder 491)
- Fundamental Studies on Dry Lubrication - Boring (Box 10, Folder 492)
- Fundamental Studies on Dry Lubrication - Boring (Box 10, Folder 493)
- Fundamental Studies on Dry-Film Lubrication (Box 10, Folder 494)
- Fundamental Studies on Dry-Film Lubrication and Coating of Test Parts (Box 10, Folder 495)
- Effect Englemann Spruce and Ponderosa Pine Dry Planer Shaving Particle Size and Shape of the Properties of Particle Board (Box 10, Folder 496)
- Flashover Tests on Iced-up High Voltage Insulators (Box 10, Folder 497)
- Flashover Tests on Iced-up High Voltage Insulators (Box 10, Folder 498)
- Police Investigation (Box 10, Folder 499)
- Investigation of 230 KV Instrument Transformer On B.P.A. System (Box 10, Folder 500)
- Weatherometer Tests on Paint (Box 10, Folder 501)
- Bloating Pitchstone (Box 10, Folder 502)
- The Case of the Shattered Milk Bottle (Box 10, Folder 503)
- Chemical and Metallurgical Analysis on Brass Sample (Box 10, Folder 504)
- Metallurgical and Chemical Examination of Metal Parts (Box 10, Folder 505)
- Metallurgical and Chemical Examination of Metal Parts (Box 10, Folder 506)
- An Investigation of the Physical and Mechanical Properties of Lebanite (Box 10, Folder 507)
- An Investigation of the Physical and Mechanical Properties of Lebanite (Box 10, Folder 508)
- Table Tests on Tungsten Jig Hutch Product (Box 10, Folder 509)
- Table Tests on Tungsten Jig Hutch Product (Box 10, Folder 510)
- Spillway Model Studies Tres Marias Project (Box 10, Folder 511)
- Spillway Model Studies Tres Marias Project (Box 10, Folder 512)
- Analysis of Hay and Grain (Box 10, Folder 513)
- Analysis of Hay and Grain for Chandler Hereford Ranch (Box 10, Folder 514)
- Fishway Studies for Rocky Reach Dam (Box 10, Folder 515)
- Water Analysis (Box 10, Folder 516)
- Sampling and Chemical Analysis of Grouting Well at (Box 10, Folder 517)
- Abrasive Resistance of Various Pipes (Box 10, Folder 518)
- Abrasive Resistance of Various Pipes (Box 10, Folder 519)
- Oil Analysis (Box 10, Folder 520)
- Corrosion Problem (Box 10, Folder 521)
- Incense Cedar and Eucalyptus Particle Boards (Box 10, Folder 522)
- Manufacture of Various Particle Boards from Planer Shavings and Slabs (Box 10, Folder 523)
- Radio-frequency Measurements - Cottonwood Butte (Box 10, Folder 524)
- Dimensional Stabilization of Red-Gum Flakeboard (Box 10, Folder 525)
- Silicone Masonry and Wood Cuttings (Box 10, Folder 526)
- Weather - 0 - Meter Tests and Consultation (Box 10, Folder 527)
- Water Analysis (Box 10, Folder 528)
- Analysis of Ceramic Glazes (Box 10, Folder 529)
- Analysis of Radiator Sludge and Antifreeze (Box 10, Folder 530)
- Arsenic Content of Hair, Nails and Beard (Box 10, Folder 531)
- Evaluation of Puncture Resistance of Boat Materials (Box 10, Folder 532)
- Furnish flakes and Particles for Research Purposes (Box 10, Folder 533)
- Extra Copies of Report (Box 10, Folder 534)
- Physical Property Tests of Brownsville Particle Board (Box 10, Folder 535)
- Noxon Rapids Stilling Basin (Box 10, Folder 536)
- Investigation of End-Gluing of Lumber (Box 10, Folder 537)
- Investigation of Linear Expansion of Allweather Siding (Box 10, Folder 538)
- Investigation of Linear Expansion of Allweather Siding (Box 10, Folder 539)
- Water Distribution City of Ellensburg (Box 10, Folder 540)
- Waterometer Test on "Curtain Wall" (Box 10, Folder 541)
- Floor Conductivity (Box 10, Folder 542)
- City of Forest Grove Water Distribution System - Mcllroy Analyzer Study (Box 10, Folder 543)
- Dust Analysis (Box 10, Folder 544)
- Temperature-Viscosity Characteristics of Continental Gear Oil (Box 10, Folder 545)
- Protein and Ash on Wheat Residue (Box 10, Folder 546)
- Fire Investigation (Box 10, Folder 547)
- Seismic System Orientation (Box 10, Folder 548)
- Seismic System Orientation (Box 10, Folder 549)
- Design, Fabricate and Test on Hydraulic Model of a Prototype Water Well (Box 10, Folder 550)
- Design, Fabricate and Test on Hydraulic Model of a Prototype Water Well (Box 10, Folder 551)
- Process Pipe Network Analysis (Box 10, Folder 552)
- Hydraulic Testing Studies Downcomer Orifice Plate and Cross- header Expansion Joint (Box 10, Folder 553)
- Design, Construct and Test Hydraulic Model of the 100-F Down- comer and Effluent System (Box 10, Folder 554)
- Design, Construct and Test Hydraulic Model of the 100-F Down- comer and Effluent System (Box 10, Folder 555)
- Hydraulic Model Tests River Pump Suction Wells 181-K Building (Box 10, Folder 556)
- Design, Development and Research Contract DDR-74 Prime Contract W-31-109-Eng-52 (Box 10, Folder 557)
- Design, Development and Research Contract DDR-74 (Box 10, Folder 558)
- Mcllroy Analysis of Pipe Network for Hanford (Box 10, Folder 559)
- Analytical Services - Export System Pipelines - 100 and 200 Areas (Special Agreement SA-115) (Box 10, Folder 560)
- Study of Fuel Residue 9/25/59 (Box 10, Folder 561)
- Suspected Arson: Lewiston, Idaho (Box 10, Folder 562)
- Study of Diesel Crankcase Sludge (Box 10, Folder 563)
- Grinding Travertine (Box 10, Folder 564)
- Evaluation Tests on Gilsonite Coating for Use on Concrete Surfaces Exposed to Sea Water (Box 10, Folder 565)
- Travel Expenses to Chicago (Box 10, Folder 566)
- Participation in Gordon Research Conferences (Box 10, Folder 567)
- Oil Analysis (Box 10, Folder 568)
- Preliminary Investigation of 525 Hardboard from European Hard- woods (Box 10, Folder 569)
- Investigation Into Producing 525 Hardboard from European Birch (Box 10, Folder 570)
- Beneficiation of Sillimanite-Andalusite Ore (Box 10, Folder 571)
- Beneficiation of Sillimanite-Andalusite Ore (Box 10, Folder 572)
- Flapreg Samples for Hamilton Manufacturing Co. (Box 10, Folder 573)
- Paintability of Medium Density Overlay Plywood (Box 10, Folder 574)
- Paintability of Medium Density Overlay Plywood (Box 10, Folder 575)
- Steady State Temperatures for KIM-I.C. Engine Jacket Fluid Heater at Low Ambients (Box 10, Folder 576)
- Thermal and Electrical Performance of a KIM-I.C. Engine Heater at Low Ambients (Box 10, Folder 577)
- Preliminary Examination of Magnesium Residue (Box 10, Folder 578)
- Brownlee Fish Barrier (Box 10, Folder 579)
- Oil Analysis (Box 10, Folder 580)
- Investigation of Broken Vacuum Cleaner Impeller (Box 10, Folder 581)
- Identify Atmospheric Corrosion Film on Copper (Box 10, Folder 582)
- Waste Paper Uses (Box 10, Folder 583)
- Load Test Manhole Covers (Box 10, Folder 584)
- Load Test on Manhole Covers (Box 10, Folder 585)
- Apply Load to Cover Failure (Box 10, Folder 586)
- Spillway Model Studies Tres Marias (Box 10, Folder 587)
- Clay Identification (Box 10, Folder 588)
- General Vibration Studies (Box 10, Folder 589)
- Aeolian Induced Vibration Studies of Greenly and Drake Conductors at Round Top Outdoor Test Span Kaiser Aluminum and Chemical Corp. (Box 10, Folder 590)
- Kaiser Fluorine Analysis (Box 10, Folder 591)
- Grinding Amphibole (Box 10, Folder 592)
- Induction Fluid Heater (Box 10, Folder 593)
- Bureau of Mines Contract (Box 11, Folder 594)
- Particleboard Overlaid Plywood (Box 11, Folder 595)
- Humidity Room Rental (Box 11, Folder 596)
- Correlation of Strength Properties of Dimension Lumber (Box 11, Folder 597)
- Evaluation of Experimental Building Panel (Box 11, Folder 598)
- Loan of Pilot Impression Finger Jointing Equipment (Box 11, Folder 599)
- Pierce Experimental Houses (Box 11, Folder 600)
- Design of Floor System for NAHB Research House * (Box 11, Folder 601)
- Instrumentation Study on Paper Overlay Process (Box 11, Folder 602)
- Destructive Flexure Tests of 50 Laminated Beams * (Box 11, Folder 603)
- Supervise Testing and Evaluation of Wood Products (Box 11, Folder 604)
- Rental of Humidity Room Space (Box 11, Folder 605)
- Evaluation of Particleboard Overlaid Plywood (Box 11, Folder 606)
- Destructive Flexure Test of Laminated Beams * (Box 11, Folder 607)
- Dumping Factor Studies on Special Building Elements *dumping? (Box 11, Folder 608)
- Wood Residue Resource Survey (Box 11, Folder 609)
- Plywood Flooring (Box 11, Folder 610)
- Product Potential of Western Samoan Wood Fiber (Box 11, Folder 611)
- Oriented Particleboard (Box 11, Folder 612)
- Structural Particleboard (Box 11, Folder 613)
- Forrest Products Research Soc. (Box 11, Folder 614)
- Short Course on Nondestructive Testing of Wood (Box 11, Folder 615)
- State Technical Program (Box 11, Folder 616)
- Nondestructive Testing of Solid Wood (Box 11, Folder 617)
- Applications of Ultrasonics to Wood Processing (Box 11, Folder 618)
- Finger Jointing of Lumber (Box 11, Folder 619)
- Particleboard Symposium (Box 11, Folder 620)
- Sound Transmission Test Facility (Box 11, Folder 621)
- Analysis of Creep Deformation of Structural Components (Box 11, Folder 622)
- E-Computer Evaluation of Lodgepole Pine (Box 11, Folder 623)
- Nondestructive Testing of Wood (Box 11, Folder 624)
- Studies on Rate Emission of DMSO from Fresh Water Algae (Box 11, Folder 625)
- Proposed School for Bridge Inspectors (Box 11, Folder 626)
- Unaccepted Proposals - Sponsored Work (Box 11, Folder 627)
- Proposed Research Program (Box 11, Folder 628)
- Unaccepted Proposals - Sponsored Work (Box 11, Folder 629)
- Unaccepted Proposals - Sponsored Work (Box 11, Folder 630)
- U.S. Air Force (Box 11, Folder 631)
- Erosion of Surfaces by Impingement of Solid Particles (Box 11, Folder 632)
- Assn. of Winds and Terrain Features w/A Class of Atmos. Infra. Waves (Box 11, Folder 633)
- IQSY Riometry Analysis (Box 11, Folder 634)
- Application of Nondestructive Testing to Particle-Type Products (Box 11, Folder 635)
- Evaluation of Use of Humans in Measuring Odor Control Technology of the Source (Box 11, Folder 636)
- Winds and Ionization (Box 11, Folder 637)
- Island County Road System Study (Box 11, Folder 638)
- NDT Evaluation of Fingerjoints (Box 11, Folder 639)
- Grant Calculation of East European Participant 1971/72 (Box 11, Folder 640)
- Contract for Hydraulic Model Studies of Downcomers (Box 11, Folder 641)
- Studies on Structures and Modeling of D-C Transmission in Buried Structures (Box 11, Folder 642)
- Hydraulic Model Studies of Downcomers (Box 11, Folder 643)
- High Voltage Insulation Measurements (Box 11, Folder 644)
- Coe Veneer Dryer Emission Study (Box 11, Folder 645)
- Prediction of Water Quality Aspects of the Wenatchee River (Box 11, Folder 646)
- Pilot Scale Investigation of Food Process Waste Treatment Character (Box 11, Folder 647)
- Polymer-Cement Concrete w/Furfuryl Alcohol Resins (Box 11, Folder 648)
- Hydraulic Model of Hydrocombine Unit (Box 11, Folder 649)
- Physical Properties of Oriented Fiberboards for Bldg. Appl (Box 11, Folder 650)
- Studded Tire Pavement Wear Reduction and Repair (Box 11, Folder 651)
- Speeches - Northwest Hardwood Assn. (1973-74) (Box 11, Folder 652)
- Prepare Sample of Green Pea Flour (Box 11, Folder 653)
- Peg Flour Preparation (Box 11, Folder 654)
- Peg Flour Patent Project (Box 11, Folder 655)
- Dallesport Hydrogeological Studies (Box 11, Folder 656)
- Hydraulic Model Studies of Downcomers (Box 11, Folder 657)
- Feasibility Study of Solidifying Radioactive Waste Materials (Box 11, Folder 658)
- Thermal Hydraulic Pilot Model Studies of the Columbia River (Box 11, Folder 659)
- Design, Development and Research Contract DDR-115 (Box 11, Folder 660)
- Determination of Concentrating Characteristics of Columbia River Humphrey Spiral Concentrates (Box 11, Folder 661)
- Evaluation of Minugel as a Plywood Adhesive Filler (Box 11, Folder 662)
- EPRDC Steering Committee Feasibility Study (Box 11, Folder 663)
- Polymer Grafting to Inorganic Substances (Box 11, Folder 664)
- Borehole Geophysical Inv. of Area Surrounding Hanford (Box 11, Folder 665)
- Nuclear Power: Evaluation of Gas Cooled Breeder Utilizing Gas Turbines (Box 11, Folder 666)
- Thermal Power Plant Waste Heat Utilization (Box 11, Folder 667)
- Modification of Prism (Box 11, Folder 668)
- Atmospheric Survey for Relative Fluoride Level (Box 11, Folder 669)
- Particleboard from Alpha Grass (Box 11, Folder 670)
- Borehole Geophysical Inv. of Area Surrounding the Hanford Atomic Energy Works (Box 11, Folder 671)
- The Role of Paper Mill Additives as Potential Stream Pollutants (Box 11, Folder 672)